uniqueauction.ae 2015-06-23

# Privacy Policy | UniqueAuction.ae

**Privacy Policy**

Personal data is data that relates to or is capable of identifying a living person. Account Holder’s privacy is very important to us and we do all we can to protect it.

The main purpose of this Privacy Policy is to make you aware of the information we may gather about you, how we may use it, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information. Words and phrases in this Privacy Policy have the same meaning as in the [Unique Auction Terms and Conditions Agreement.](http://www.uniqueauction.ae/terms)

**General Information**

When you join Unique Auction your personal data will be collected, processed, stored and used by us to provide customer support, process payments we make to Account Holders and for other purposes referred to in this Privacy Policy, the Unique Auction Terms and Conditions Agreement and any other agreements that Account Holders may have with us.

**The information we collect**

**Personal data:**

When you first sign-up for the Unique Auction, we ask for your name and email address and other personal information including your choice of payment method. In addition we usually also capture your IP address. Other personal information about you is then optional to provide.

We will retain your personal data for as long as is permitted for legal, regulatory and fraud prevention purposes.

**Cookies:**

When your web browser accesses a specific web site such as ours, cookies (a type of small text file) may, depending on your browser settings, be automatically stored on your computer's hard drive.

Cookies on the Unique Auction website do the following:

Tell us the route (such as a web-search or an online advertisement, for example) by which you came to the Unique Auction site.

Where you are an Account Holder:

Keep you logged in to your Account for a period of time.

Allow us to comply with your choices about the display of information in your Account.

Track your use of blogging functionality available through the Unique Auction site.

Remember the options you select 

Permit integration with social media sites (such as the ability to "like" Unique Auction on Facebook).

We believe that the cookies you encounter on the Unique Auction site are either (i) necessary to perform the functions that Account Holders wish to use the Unique Auction Service for, or (ii) are non-intrusive.

To learn how to manage and remove cookies, please go to [www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

Please note, however, that if you set your browser to reject cookies you may not be able to use certain aspects of Unique Auction.

**Security**

We're committed to protecting your personal information. All information that you provide to us is stored on secure servers and access to this database is restricted internally. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we use reduce the possibility of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

Access to your Account is password-protected for your privacy and security. While we do our best to protect your personal information you also must protect yourself. What does this mean?

Keep your password or other access information secret.

Ensure no-one else uses Unique Auction while your machine is "signed in" to the Unique Auction site.

Make sure you sign out from your Account when not using it. 

We may share (whether or not for payment) aggregated demographic information with our partners, clients and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When you sign up for these services, we will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

We may also use such aggregated information and statistics for monitoring the Website usage in order to help us develop Website and our services and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. 

**Editing your Account and mailing settings**

We like to keep in touch with our Account Holders so after you have signed up to Unique Auction we'll send you information about products or services provided by us.

Of course we know lots of emails can be annoying so we try to keep ours to a minimum. However, if you feel you're getting too many or would like more you can change the settings in your Account at any time. Each communication gives you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving similar future communications. You can review, change or correct your identity and email address information by signing into your Account and going to the settings tab.

Please note there are some communications that are an integral part of the Unique Auction and cannot be opted-out of. These communications cover, amongst other things, changes to the Unique Auction and your actual or potential transactions.
